Guide to the Larry Hama Comic Book Collection 1967- 2011 MSS.337
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Comic Books and Periodicals
  - Subseries C: Various
    - The 'Nam, May 1999 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Neck & Cold (3) [Spanish], Julio 1996 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Nick Fury: Who is Scorpio?, November 2000 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Official Xbox Magazine, August 2002 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Our Army at War (194,263), June 1968- December 1973 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Peter Porker, The Spectuacular Spider-Ham (vol.1, no. 1-2,4,5,13,15,17), May 1985- September 1987 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Planet of Vampires (vol.1, no.1), February 1975 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - The Punisher Armory (vol.1, no.1,9), July 1990- April 1994 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - The Punisher: War Zone (vol.1, no. 20-21), October 1993- November 1993 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Resident Evil: Fire and Ice 2, February 2001 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Return to the Amalgam Age of Comics: the DC Comics Collection, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Sabretooth (1-4), August 1993- November 1993 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Sabretooth, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Savage Tales (1,2,6,7), October 1985- October 1986 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Secret Identities: The Asian American Superhero Anthology Preview, Coming Fall 2008 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Secret Invasion No.1, June 2008 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Secrets of Sinister House (vol.3, no.10), March 1973 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - SGT. Rock: The Lost Battalion (2-3), February 2009- March 2009 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Showcase Presents: Enemy Ace Volume One, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Showcase Presents: Secrets of Sinister House, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Snake Eyes: Declassified (vol.II, issue 1-2), August 2005- September 2005 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Spider-Man: Venom Agenda (vol.1, no.1), January 1998 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Spirit of Ninja (vol.1, number 3), January 1987 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Spookes (vol.2, no.3-4), April 2008- May 2008 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Spooks Omega Team (vol.1, no.1), July 2008 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Spooks Omega Team (vol.2), January 2009 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Star Hunters (2), December- January 1977/1978 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Star Wars (48), June 1981 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Steeltown Rockers (1,2,5), April 1990- August 1990 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Storm Shadow (1,2), May 2007- June 2007 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Storm Shadow (3,4), July 2007- August 2007 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Storm Shadow (5), September 2007 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Storm Shadow (6,7), October 2007- November 2007 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Storm Shadow (vol.1: solo), January 2008 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Tarzan (vol.25, no.210), July 1972 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Toyfare: The Toy Magazine (102,105,135), February 2006- November 2008 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Toyfare: The Toy Magazine (139,145,146), March 2009- October 2009 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - The Transformers Universe (1), December 1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - [The Trojan Rabbit] [Russian], [October 2006] (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Veneno: Redencion (5) [Spanish], 1995 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Venom: Carnage Unleashed (vol.1, no.3), June 1995 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Venom: The Finale (vol.1, no.1-2), November 1997- December 1997 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Venom: Sinner Takes All (vol.1, no.4), November 1995 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Walt Disney's Comics and Stories (vol.16, no.1), October 1955 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Walt Disney Donald Duck (no.212), October 1979 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Walt Disney's Uncle Scrooge (vol.1, no.211), November 1986 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Wetworks (1), June 1994 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Wizard: The Guide to Comics (19,38), March 1993- October 1994 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - The Wizard (65), January 1997 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Wolfpack (vol.1, no.1-3), August 1988- October 1988 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Wolfpack, [1987] (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Wulf the Barbarian (1,2), February 1975- April 1975 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Young Lust (5), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Young Master (1,2), 1987 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Young Master (3,4), March 1988- May 1988 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Series II: Drafting Materials and Creative Work
  - Bucky 1991 Original Visuals (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Bucky 1991 Larry's Dossiers (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Bucky 1992 Original Visuals (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Bucky 1992 Larry's Dossiers (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Bucky 1999 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Bucky TV, undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Bucky Video, undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Sci-Fi Ducks, undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Info G.I. Joe, undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - [G.I. Joe], undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Wolverine, undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Shiloh [Osprey Graphic History], undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - [Cops/ G.I. Joe], undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - "G.I. Joe Writer to Recieve Kiyama Award at Asian American ComiCon", 2009 (Box 8, Folder 40)